

CONTACT

- +33 6 68 45 93 80
- efaujour@gmail.com
- 74370 ARGONAY, France
- in /elisabeth-faujour
- /ElisabethFir
- /elisabethfaujour.vercel.app

SKILLS

HTML | CSS

SASS

Javascript

Typescript

React | Next.js

Redux

Node.js | Express

SQL | PostgreSQL

ORM Sequelize

Git | GitHub

SCRUM | AGILE

SOFT-SKILLS

Curiosity

Logical thinking

Organization

Relational

Autonomy

INTERESTS

Health & prevention

Mutlipalyer video games

Moutaine hiking

Piano & clarinet

Support for animal welfare

ELISABETH FAUJOUR

Javascript Web Developer

After 7 years as a Physiotherapist, I decided to broaden my professional horizons by transitioning into Web Development, specializing in Javascript. Thus, I acquired a solid skills base and enhanced my sensibilty to UX-UI Design. Versatile and driven by excellence and continuous improvement, I am eager to contribute my commitment and creativity to innovative projects.



EXPERIENCE

Next.js Developer - Personal Project

January 2024

Portfolio Redesign.

- Technologies : Next.js | Typescript | SCSS
- Skills : responsive design, SVG, XML, animations, SEO, accessibility

Front-End Developer - Final Year Project (O'Clock)

Sept 2023 - Oct 2023

Development of an interactive travel organization application. The project was completed in 1 month, with a team of 5 developers and based on SCRUM and AGILE methodologies.

- Roles: Lead Dev Front & Produt Owner
- Technologies: React | Redux | Typescript | SCSS | Vite | Node.js | Express | PostgreSQL
- Skills: SPA, RESTful API, axios, JWT authentication, Vercel deployment, responsive design, accessibility, SEO, GDPR

Physsiotherapist

June 2016 - April 2023

Assistant-collaborator in physio group practices: providing active care in the practice and at home, administrative and material management, accounting management, software proficiency in Vega, Topaze, Kine4000, Doctolib, specialization in Mechanical Diagnosis and Therapy - McKenzie Institute®.



EDUCATION

RNCP Level 5 Title 'Web and Mobile Web Developer'

May 2023 - Nov 2023

O'Clock School - Fullstack JavaScript Web Developer

- 3 months of skills base
- 1 month of Front-end specialization: React
- 1 month of professional group project: O'Journey

Diploma of Physiotherapist

Sept 2013 - June 2016

Physiotherapy School of the University Hospital of Grenoble

PACES - First Year Common to Health Studies

Sept 2011 - June 2013

University Grenobles Alpes - Faculty of Medicine